
var questions = [{

  question: "How many goals did Thierry Henry score in his career at Arsenal?",
  choices : ["249", "174","185", "226"],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
{
  question: "Marouane Chamakh joined Arsenal in 2010. Which country is he from?",
  choices: ["Morocco", "Germany", "Tunisia", "Egypt"],
  correctAnswer: 0
},
{
  question: "Jose Antonio Reyes signed for Arsenal in January 2004. From which club was the talented left-footer signed?",
  choices: ["Lazio", "Real Betis", "Roma", "Sevilla"],
  correctAnswer: 3
},
 {
  question: "How many Arsenal players that started the 1998 FA Cup final also started the 2002 FA Cup final against Chelsea?",
  choices: ["4", "3", "2", "5"],
   correctAnswer: 0
 },
 {
   question: "From May 2003 to October 2004, Arsenal went unbeaten in the Premier League. Across how many games were they unbeaten?",
   choices: ["38", "42", "45", "49"],
   correctAnswer: 3
 },
 {
   question: "Arsenal won the Double in 2001-02 campaign. Which player's goal at Old Trafford won Arsenal the Double that season?",
   choices: ["Thierry Henry", "Sylvain Wiltord", "Dennis Bergkamp", "Tony Adams"],
   correctAnswer: 1
 },
 {
   question: "Andrei Arshavin, a winger and second striker is from which country?",
   choices: ["Ukraine", "Russia", "Belarus", "Andorra"],
   correctAnswer: 1
 },
  {
    question: "What team did Marc Overmars and Emmanual Petit both join after leaving Arsenal?",
    choices: ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Deportivo La Coruna", "Alaves"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
   {
     question: "Dennis Bergkamp played 316 games at league level for Arsenal. Which country did he come from?",
     choices: ["Denmark", "Norway", "Sweden", "Netherlands"],
     correctAnswer: 3
   },
    {
      question: "Who scored Arsenal's only goal in the 2006 Champions League final?",
      choices: ["Thierry Henry", "Sol Campbell", "Cesc Fabregas", "Robert Pires"],
      correctAnswer: 1
    }  ];
